If we're starting
dang. I do that all the time. My bad. I am I am so sorry. So
let's redo this. Tom Vanderbilt Board of Selectmen special meeting, Friday, February 17, 7PM.
We're gonna call the meeting to order,
and we're gonna start with the Pledge of Allegiance.
I pledge allegiance to the flag of The United States Of America and to the republic for which it stands,
one nation under God, indivisible
with liberty and justice for all.
We're gonna move on to public speak. I'm not sure that we have anybody from the public that's not involved in this meeting. Anybody?
No? Okay. Public speak is done.
We're gonna move that we move to executive session to discuss a union grievance.
I got a second.
Second.
All those in favor?
Hold on. Be before you do it, can I suggest that you invite the union attorney, Lauren Defoe,
as well as the public works,
union members and myself,
if you so choose, into the
You know I would be happy to invite all the parties? So, miss Tafoe,
union members, and, the town administrator
for Andover, Eric Anderson,
are cordially invited to our executive session.
So, Scott, do you still second that? Yes, sir. Alright. So all in favor?
Aye.
Thank you, Paul. Eric, can I